Hello everyone we are Policy welcome to our
channel and today in this video I will
tell you about ICICI Bru i Protect Smart
if you want to take any health or term
insurance plan then you
can click on the link given in the description box and
take your insurance plan without any spam or gimmicks.
Let us now start with the
details of today's plan.  ICICI Pro Eye
Protect Smart.  This product is
reasonably priced compared to other plans in the market
and
offers multiple customization options for receiving the claim amount.
But it has limited pay options
and lacks some essential customisations like
increasing cover.  It has a critical
illness rider.  This is an accelerated rider.
Meaning you will get it as an advance from the payout base cover.
Talking about claim settlement, there are very few claim settlement complaints against ICICI Insurance Company in this plan.
But according to our research, we have received more
complaints regarding policy purchase as
compared to other insurance companies.
If you want flexibility and extra
customizations, then
definitely compare all the options before taking this plan.
Cheaper than other products in the market, this
plan comes with affordable pricing.
Claim payout customization is also available in it.  This
means that multiple options
are available so that you can customize the payout structure for your family.
Exit
option with refund means that if you
want to exit the plan while it is active,
you can also get a refund of your paid premiums
in this plan.  It has a better claim
settlement track record.  This means that the number of claim
settlement complaints against the insurance company is
less as compared to other insurance companies.  If you are
looking for budget-friendly insurance that
offers flexible payout and exit options,
then this plan can be a good option for you.
This insurance company
offers fast claim settlement and high claim
approval rate.  In which
96.91% claims are settled within just 30 days
and
99.17% claims are approved.  Additionally,
financial stability is strong with a solvency ratio of 192%.
Complaints wise, only 0.10% of
customers
expressed dissatisfaction with their claim experience.  But the death claim
form is quite lengthy which
makes the process TDS.  Personal relationship manager
and home pickup service are also available,
which may be a drawback for some customers.
However, the plan also comes with online claim tracking
and dedicated toll-free support,
which adds to the convenience.
You can apply for this plan from a minimum of 18 years to a maximum of 65 years.  You
can take cover till 99 years.  That means
ultra long term protection.  This plan does
not offer the option of automatic cover increase.
To increase the coverage, a new policy will have to be taken.
You can also take it monthly.  You can
also pay premium on half yearly or yearly basis for a limited period.
After which
you can enjoy life long cover.
You will get three riders in this plan.
Critical Illness Rider, Claim, Pay Out,
Customization, Waiver of Premium Rider.  If
you enjoyed this video, don't forget to give us a like
and subscribe to PolicyX.
Till then bye-bye and take care.